Link can be found in the description.
But now we jump in right away.
Number 1: Brass bull
The brass bulls were manufactured during ancient Greece
and used as a torture and execution tool.
It was a device shaped like a hollow bull,
Made of bronze or by brass.
The punished person was locked inside the bull through a gap in the side.
Then you lit a fire under the bull.
When the metal got hot, the person would
Inside slowly roasted alive.
The bull was designed in a way where one had made holes in the bull's mouth
or in the nostrils and when the punished screamed in there the sound came
out of there and distorted it to a sound similar to a bull
Beeing ..
Number 2: Gillotin.
Guillotine was a device
that consisted of two large vertical rails and a large heavy
Blade placed at the top, also called car.
The penalty's head was placed in a bracket and then
If you dropped down the blade which then cut off the head from the body.
It was important that the blade was angled so that it created a
Cutting movement over the neck.
If the blade was straight then it could happen that it punished
Number 5: Ratbrene
The rat cage
was a horrible execution method used during the Middle Ages.
The punished person was tied on to a platform
Or in a chair with a cage placed over the stomach.
Then they placed starved rats in the cage
and by heat it up from the outside, the rats were forced to gnaw
And scratch through the person's body in a desperate attempt to escape.
The rats bit and tore through the body on the punished person
Until it finally died.
Number six walled.
And maybe another one.
In the end, the weight became so great that the body of the punished person
was crushed.
Number 9: Death by melted metal.
This method of execution meant that one poured melted
metal such as lead or bronze,
down the throat of the punished.
The extreme heat caused severe burns,
resulting in enormous pain
And finally death.
Talk about heartburn.